I'm so happy right now,
because you all are with me.
Let's be friends forever.
Kanade. I love you.
I'm never letting you go.
I feel the same.
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered.
What?
Kanade's dad was--
Don't say it!
Why did Kaori…
Depending on what you say,
my son might need a lawyer.
Masaki, wait! Don't go!
I'm the one who…
Someone who I thought loved me
disappeared from in front of me again.
The patient is male
in his twenties or thirties.
Identity is currently unknown.
-There's something I want to tell you.
-What?
I must go somewhere…
Kanade Nishimura, how many years
have you been a prosecutor?
Sorry?
How long have you been doing this?
Six years and three months.
You've been a prosecutor
for six and a half years.
Do you truly think
a deposition from an accomplice
is sufficient to go to trial?
I was prosecuting a case
involving illegal drug deals
that occurred a week ago.
-Police!
-Don't move!
The Kanagawa Prefectural Police
obtained information on drug deals
being made at a bar in Yokohama.
The police raided
a private room in the bar
and three men were arrested at the scene.
One of them was the second son
of Akihiko Kawagoe,
the Secretary-General
of the Democratic Liberal Party.
The case suddenly became
the center of public attention.
But Takumi Kawagoe was the only one
of the three men arrested
who didn't have drugs on him,
and denied the accusation.
He insisted he didn't know anything.
No, not exactly.
It's just that the other suspects
admitted to the crime.
His statement has many inconsistencies.
Witnesses saw him frequenting the bar.
Above all, he was in the small room
while the drugs were being sold.
You don't have to tell me.
I've read what you wrote.
But you don't have his confession.
He was not in possession of any drugs.
Right.
Either get him to confess…
or collect stronger evidence.
You're not an amateur.
I've heard that
Kanade Nishimura is good. But…
Is this all you have to show?
We needed an indictment
in this case at all costs.
Two years since getting transferred
to Yokohama.
The city's night sky is too light
to see any stars.
Mr. Nogi.
You're not allowed to leave your room
without permission.
What are you doing?
Hmm? I was just looking at the stars.
Stars?
Nurse Hashimoto,
when can I leave the hospital?
-Excuse me?
-Um…
Hasn't this healed enough?
It's not for me to say.
What did the doctor say?
Nothing.
Should I ask him?
Yes, thank you.
Confession.
Evidence.
Evidence…
BAR GLOIRE
NAKA-KU, YOKOHAMA
The sight of illegal drug transactions…
I'M KENTA, A REGULAR!
KENTA NAKAZAWA
MIZUHARA
I FOUND KENTA! I'LL LEAVE A LINK.
EIICHI NAKAMURA
NAN-SAN
Huh?
Have you been to Bar Gloire before?
It was my first time there.
-I'm home.
-Hi, Takashi.
-Still working?
-Mm-hmm.
Don't work too hard.
Here. You've got lines right there.
You know what, Kanade?
Hmm? What?
Don't you think… it's time we get married?
He proposed to me as if he were saying
"good morning" or "good night."
Good night.
Good night…
Get married… huh?
12TH ANNIVERSARY BUDDHIST
MEMORIAL SERVICE FOR KAORI OIKAWA
It's been 12 years since Kaori's accident.
Masaki disappeared that day,
and I became an empty shell.
Careful!
Where are you going?
I got a call from a girl.
What?
Just kidding. To the store.
I'll be right back.
You'll be right back…
That's what you said.
NOTIFICATION OF REJECTION
I was alive,
but I felt as though I were dead.
It felt futile no matter how hard I tried.
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
-I-I'm sorry.
-Take your time.
I'm sorry.
Here.
It's just hot water, but it will warm you.
This is good.
It was
magical hot water.
He gave me back
the will to live.
Is this seat taken?
No.
How are you doing?
I'm better, thank you.
Good.
Um…
Thank you so much
for your help the other day.
It's nothing.
SHINANO UNIVERSITY
Careful.
-Are you okay?
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Hello.
My hospital is over there.
I-I'm a legal apprentice at Tokyo District
Public Prosecutors Office.
Oh, so you passed it.
The bar exam.
Yes.
-Cheers.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you very much.
-That's good.
-Ahh.
Should I start cooking?
-Oh, I'll do it.
-No, I can do it.
Another year went by
before we started dating.
But being a rookie prosecutor,
I was transferred outside of Tokyo.
And he was too busy at his hospital.
Sorry. An emergency patient.
I don't think I can make it tonight.
Okay. Good luck with your work.
I'm not free next week.
How about the week after?
I have to go to Fukuoka
for a conference that week.
How about this weekend?
A case I'm on is entering the homestretch.
No time to go to Tokyo.
Dr. Okuda. The preparation
for the examination is done.
Thank you.
Is it ever going to work out for us?
There were times
when I almost gave up on dating him.
KAEDE, I'LL BE HOME LATE
SO NO DINNER TONIGHT
He went to work without even
hearing my answer to his proposal.
Was he feeling awkward
after all this time?
Or was he just expecting
for me to say yes?
OUTRAGEOUS SON
OF THE SECRETARY-GENERAL OF DLP
HIS CIRCLE OF FRIENDS
AND DRUG ACQUISITION CHANNELS
TOMO
It's been a while. How are you?
Kaori's 12th Anniversary Memorial Service
is on Sunday. Are you coming?
Yes, I'm planning to.
Okay, I'll talk to you then.
I know you're busy.
It's fine. I look forward to seeing you.
However, I had to work
on that day after all.
PRINT
The illegal drug dealing case.
This witness interview
is the key to the indictment.
The bar owner where the drug deal
took place is the witness.
BAR GLOIRE OWNER
TOSHIKI TAGAWA, AGE 49
I'm sorry, but I unexpectedly
have a witness interview.
I might be late.
I'll take the bullet train
as soon as I'm done.
I see.
It must be tough working on a Sunday.
Best of luck.
That day, Tomo said
our friendship might be over.
But as we got together
for Kaori's first, second, and sixth
anniversary memorial services,
our relationship began
to return to what it was.
Mr. Tagawa, the witness, has arrived.
Thank you. I'll be right there.
Sometimes I wonder what it would be like
if Tomo had become a prosecutor.
But after she passed
the entrance exam for law school,
she simply gave up on the bar exam.
The reason was her pregnancy.
And the father was…
Hey, can I wear this today?
No, you have to wear black.
But it's the 12th, and a private event--
-Wear black.
-Yes.
Hey, can I wear this today?
Thank you for coming on your day off.
Well…
You know, our customers
were the ones arrested.
My bar just got caught up in it.
Of course, we understand.
We are asking for your cooperation.
Mr. Tagawa, when the police
questioned you,
you said you didn't know Takumi Kawagoe.
That's right. I didn't know him.
The son of the Secretary-General
of the DLP?
The press is making a big fuss
and it's a nuisance to us.
I see.
Mr. Tagawa, you must have heard
about a bar named La Bilance.
Until three years ago,
you owned a bar at the same location
under a different name.
And the name was La Bilance.
Is this correct?
Uh. Yes.
This means the current bar
reopened with a different name.
Don't you know a man
named Eiichi Nakamura?
I do. He was a regular at the last bar.
NAKAMON
EIICHI NAKAMURA
This is from Mr. Nakamura's social media.
If you follow the links back in time,
he was at a party
at La Bilance four years ago.
And you were there too.
OWNER AND FRIENDS
A PRIVATE FAREWELL PARTY
Huh?
And the person
who is next to you in the picture…
POST BY @NAKAMURAXX983
…is Takumi Kawagoe,
the suspect. Is it not?
Have you been to Bar Gloire before?
It was my first time there.
Why were you hiding this fact from us?
Because I…
Mr. Tagawa.
You can lie to us all you want.
But if you keep this up,
we will consider you complicit
in the dealing of illegal drugs.
Furthermore, we will have to view you
as providing the location
and assisting in the dealing
of illegal drugs.
Is that all right with you?
No, I…
Kaji, today's deposition should do it,
can you prepare the indictment?
Yes, ma'am. But do I have
to work overtime on my own?
-I'll buy you lunch.
-No need for that.
Can I have a paid day off instead?
You're always telling me I can,
but it never happens.
Kaji, isn't it an assistant officer's job
to prepare the indictment?
Uh, yes.
You'll get your day off.
I'm counting on you.
-Goodbye.
Thank you both for making time
in your busy schedule to come.
Not at all.
Mr. and Mrs. Oikawa,
I hope you both stay well.
Thank you.
-Take care of yourself, Tomomi.
-I will.
If only that accident hadn't happened,
Kaori would be like you two by now--
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I guess it's no use
talking about it in this way.
It's all right.
I hope you'll find happiness,
for Kaori's sake too.
And I hope sometimes
you'll remember Kaori.
I've never forgotten her.
Not ever.
We'll come by to see you again.
-Please do.
-Thank you.
Looks like Kanade couldn't make it.
There are people you can only interview
on weekends, I guess.
Having a job is not easy.
Well, it can't be helped.
"Be happy for Kaori's sake too," she said.
-Huh?
-I was just wondering.
How can I find happiness for Kaori's sake?
Hey, Mom.
I know where you want to go.
Railway Heritage Park, right?
Yay! Abt system!
Let's go, hurry!
How did he get so simple-minded?
Maybe the existence of that kid
is our happiness.
What?
Should we get ourselves
some soda floats and head home?
Uhh… Wasn't that a little cheesy?
-Why would I be?
-Hmm?
GRAVE OF OIKAWA FAMILY
MELON SODA FLOAT
SHINANO UNIVERSITY
After that, I visited the university
for the first time in a while.
Although it was Sunday,
I saw some students there.
Similar to how we were back then.
Hey, stop!
That's the seat where Kaori
was always drinking melon soda floats.
-Give me.
-Aww.
Hey, don't.
Tastes terrible.
-Who cares what you think? I like it.
-How can you drink so much of that crap?
-Masaki is mine!
-What are you talking about?
Kanade too! You're mine!
I like both of you!
-Ah-ha!
-What are you doing?
-Tomo is mine too!
-Don't be silly.
How about me?
Yuki? I don't think so.
What? That's mean!
Yuki, come here.
Are you kidding me?
We were so innocent then.
We all liked Kaori.
She was high-maintenance, audacious,
and childlike.
But we liked her nonetheless.
Then why…
To the store.
I'll be right back.
This accident…
Do you suppose it was a crime?
I wonder if they suspect
it wasn't just an accident.
What really happened
between those two at that time?
The accident was blamed
on Kaori's negligence.
Hey! Tell me what happened!
I'm the one who…
Masaki…
was saying something to me.
What did he say?
What was he telling me?
What do you mean he's gone?
As I said,
the bed was empty before I realized it.
And I found this.
THANKS FOR THE CARE
MEDICAL FEE, NOGI
What's the matter?
Oh, Dr. Okuda. Well,
a patient brought in as an emergency case
left the hospital without permission.
Can't you contact him?
I'm sorry.
Dr. Okuda,
the patient's family has arrived.
Yes, thank you.
MASAKI NOGI, ADMITTED: JULY 11, 2024
PHYSICIAN: DR. KENTARO NAKAMURA
Wrong room.
Sorry, my mistake.
Are you kidding?
Why?
Why are you here?
Did you know
about Kaori's Memorial Service?
Was it you who went to her grave?
I wondered how long it had been
since I uttered the name Masaki?
Kanade.
The moment I heard his voice,
I was instantly back in those days.
I missed you.
What's that?
After all these years…
What are you saying now?
Where were you this whole time?
And what were you doing?
Masaki.
Kanade…
are you a prosecutor now?
Huh?
That lapel pin.
Yes, I've become one.
That's amazing.
You kept at it.
Yes.
I kept at it.
I felt like I wanted to die at one point.
I thought I couldn't believe anyone.
You don't know…
how hard it was for me…
how hard it was for us
to get over the death of Kaori.
Why did you disappear without telling us?
Why didn't you say anything?
How awful of you.
So don't you dare tell me now
that you missed me.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
Hey, don't cry.
Sorry.
Wait.
Back then…
what did you say to me?
On that day when I last saw you.
What went on with you and Kaori?
Why did Kaori…
Kanade.
You're amazing.
Seriously.
I think you're amazing.
I was relieved the light was turned off.
I didn't want to face Takashi
feeling the way I did.
Sorry I missed you today.
Come visit us when you have more time.
A gathering to remember Kaori.
Thanks. Sounds great.
By the way,
I saw Masaki today.
I ran into him at--
TOMO
Hello.
-What do you mean you saw him?
-W-Wait a second.
Well, I saw Masaki.
-Where?
-The university.
I didn't make it to the memorial service,
so I visited Kaori's grave.
Then after that,
I felt like seeing the university.
What's that guy doing now?
I don't know.
Did he know that it was
the day of Kaori's service?
I asked him the same question.
So, what'd he say?
He said, "Sorry."
That's all he said.
He disappeared again after that.
Hey Mom. I need
my gym clothes for tomorrow.
What? You're just telling me now?
Ask your father.
-What?
-Sorry. I was talking to my son.
Anyway, I can't believe it.
It's like, "Screw you!" Right?
Mom. Dad's asleep.
All right. I'll take care of it now.
Sorry. I'll call you later.
Hey, you've got to come over soon.
Let's talk all about it.
Yeah. Okay, see you then.
-Hey, Kanade.
-Sorry, what?
You'd better not see Masaki.
You have Takashi now.
I won't see him.
I don't have his number--
Absolutely not. You should never see him.
I know.
-Yeah.
-Bye then.
-Okay, bye. Good night.
Is something the matter?
Umm, uh, I was just talking with Tomo.
Sorry if I woke you.
-No.
-Oh.
Uh, I wanted to ask you
about what I said the other day.
What?
About us getting married.
Yeah.
When's your next day off?
Well… It'll be after
the case I'm on now has been resolved.
Let's visit your mother together
and tell her about it on your day off.
Sounds good.
Hey.
Whoa. What are you doing over there?
I couldn't get to sleep.
Kanade said
she ran into Masaki today.
What? No way.
What could he be thinking
after all these years?
Are you listening?
Yeah. I'm listening.
Here.
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered.
Do you want to die with me?
Kanade's dad was--
Don't say it!
So you're saying
you obtained the bar owner's statement
to corroborate the crime?
Yes.
Now Masuko and Ikeguchi's confessions
have been substantiated.
There is no doubt
that Takumi Kawagoe was an accomplice.
Are you sure you can win the case?
Yes.
I see.
Excuse me. Ms. Nishimura.
The witness from the other day
says he can't testify in court.
What do you mean?
He says he made a mistake.
You must be joking.
I kept asking him repeatedly
but he suddenly started to play dumb.
Hello.
-Can you explain?
-He called just moments ago.
Oh… I see.
Yes.
So that's what's happening.
Understood.
Takumi Kawagoe has switched
his attorney to Koichiro Nogi.
This is a tough one.
It's not rare
for the defense counsel to change.
The former prosecutor
has come out to squash us, huh?
How do you feel about the arrest?
Since the accused is the son of Democratic
Liberal Party Secretary-General,
they seem to be very eager.
However,
it was a completely rash move
by the police.
Are you saying
the arrest itself was a mistake?
I think it was an unjust arrest.
I believe the prosecution
will not indict under these circumstances.
An indictment is impossible.
There's just no way.
So Takumi Kawagoe
has no involvement with this case?
Of course not.
That man. It's Masaki's father.
Huh?
The man on TV
was Masaki's father
who came to see him after the accident.
Did Mr. Kawagoe frequent that bar?
No comment.
Is the Secretary-General…
But that was not all.
I had a feeling I had seen
a similar scene somewhere before.
The case is a fabrication
by the prosecution.
The chief prosecutor forced a confession.
It is outrageous.
It was a fragment in my memory
so faint that I couldn't recall it.
-He's here!
-There he is!
In the end, the son
of the Secretary-General of the DLP
Takumi Kawagoe was released
without indictment
and the case was later dropped.
ADDITIONAL RELATED DOCUMENTS
YOKOHAMA DISTRICT COURT
YOKOHAMA SUMMARY COURT
Thank you very much
for all your hard work.
Don't mention it.
-Goodbye.
I have…
something to ask you.
This is out of the blue.
Do you have some time?
All right. Let's go over there.
That patient who ran away the other day?
The patient who was brought in
with blows to the head and stomach.
You still haven't been able
to contact him?
No.
The cell phone number never connects,
and he has no fixed address.
Masaki Nogi…
Where were you? What have you been doing?
Haven't you thought about how much
your family would be worried about you?
-Masaki.
-I'm not a kid.
So stop treating me like one.
What I wanted to ask you is…
about a former Tokyo district prosecutor,
Eisuke Tsuji.
Twenty years ago,
he committed suicide
right before his arrest
in the environmental energy
corruption case.
I don't know what you're doing now,
but did you come to see me
just to talk about something like that?
You've been missing
for over ten years, and now this?
There's nothing I can tell you.
Why are you always like that?
You always disappoint me.
Are you able to feed yourself?
-Are you making a living--
-Don't change the subject.
All I want
is to know the truth.
I'm in trouble if I don't know it.
Is somebody
making you do this?
Don't pry with stupid questions.
Wait.
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered.
I said wait.
You shouldn't be seeing Kanade!
What the hell is this?
-This is nuts!
-Why won't you believe me?!
What's your problem?
Let go of me!
Kaori!
Kanade's dad was--
Don't say it!
Weren't you the one who killed him?
Did you kill Eisuke Tsuji?
Say something!
You killed Eisuke Tsuji, didn't you?
That's why
that accident…
And I…
Kaori was…
The past that I had sealed off
suddenly came rushing back.
Subtitle translation by: Ikuko Sachs
My father was killed.
Why do you think your father didn't fight?
What does that have to do
with Kaori Oikawa's death?
Sometimes the past needs to be sealed.
Marry me.
-You'd better not get close to Kanade.
-Kanade!
I must not go. I know I shouldn't, but…